We build AI commercials.
We're at 250K this year.
We're basically at 25K an ad.
You charge 25,000 for those ads?
Yeah.
Fuck, man.
Well, the price point that we want to be at is 50K.
So our sales value prop is, you know,
we start at price anchoring that a normal
broadcast commercial, 500K.
The initial idea was, you know,
we're one-tenth the price at 50K,
bringing the same industry expertise
and quality and fidelity.
I would say we're around like 18K
as far as an actual 30-second commercial,
as far as cost.
I don't think there's anything special about AI.
People want customers.
Whether it's, I have a flaming stick
that I wave and customers come,
smoke signals, wacky waveable inflatable arm guy,
no one cares, right?
As long as they get customers.
If anything, it's like, I almost want the fact
that you have AI to be a secret.
I'd rather just sell it for 500 grand
and then have it cost 18 and then be like, awesome.